(Bernadette:)My dad's pretty insistent on it,
though.
Why don't I talk to your dad?
- Man to man.
- Really?
- Oh, that'd be so great. Heh.
- Done.
I should probably give you a heads up
about a couple things.
(Bernadette:)Even though he's retired from
the police force, he still carries his gun.
(Bernadette:)But don't worry, he won't shoot it.
It's more of a fashion statement.
Okay, heh.
(Bernadette:)And just to be safe,
when you talk to him...
(Bernadette:)...don't bring up Jimmy Carter,
gardeners...
(Bernadette:)...foreign people, homosexuals,
Sean Penn, Vatican ll, gun controI...
(Bernadette:)...organic food,
the designated hitter rule...
(Bernadette:)...recycling
or the fact that you're Jewish.
(Howard:)Got it, got it.
Will you e-mail me that list, heh?
(Bernadette:)So the thing to watch for,
if he's shouting at you, you're okay.
(Bernadette:)But if he starts to get real quiet...
(Bernadette:)...leave as quickly as you can
without making eye contact.
(Bernadette:)Not in a straight line,
throw some zigs and zags in there.
(Howard:)You know, this isn't that pressing.
(Howard:)Why don't I talk to him about it
in May, heh?
(Bernadette:)In May you're gonna be on
the International Space Station.
They got a phone.